[upbeat music]
[excited chatter]
Aw, look at the kids,
哦，看看这些孩子们，
all excited for Good Sporty's first superhero birthday party.
都对Good Sporty的第一个超级英雄生日派对兴奋不已。
Aw, so cute.
哦，真可爱。
They actually wish they had superpowers.
他们其实都希望自己有超能力。
You thinking what I'm thinking?
你在想我在想的事吗？
Yeah, I totally wish I had superpowers.
是啊，我真希望我有超能力。
- Yeah. - Me too.
- 是啊。 - 我也是。
If I was a superhero,
如果我是超级英雄，
I'd be all jacked with super strength.
我会变得力大无穷。
[grunts]
嗯……
[Dawn] If I was a superhero, I'd have super speed.
【道恩】如果我是超级英雄，我会拥有超高速度。
[Nicky] My superpower would be to fly.
【尼基】我的超能力会是飞行。
[Ricky] I'd be able to manipulate people with my mind.
【里奇】我能用意念控制人。
- Stop hitting yourself. all: Ow.
【里奇】- 打自己。所有人：哎哟。
Anyone else think superhero Ricky is a jerk?
有没有人觉得超级英雄里奇是个讨厌鬼？
[gasps] Oh, my goodness.
[惊呼] 哦，我的天哪。
Are you all here for the party?
你们都是来参加派对的吗？
[all] Yeah.
[所有人] 是的。
Wow, there are so many of you.
哇，你们这么多人。
How will I host all by myself?
我一个人怎么招待啊？
Help!
帮帮我！
Heeeelp!
帮帮忙！
[triumphant music]
[胜利的音乐]
Have no fear, lady citizen!
不要害怕，女士市民！
I'll make sure that birthday boy Stevie
我会确保生日男孩史蒂维
and all his friends have the most fun ever,
确保史蒂夫和他的朋友们度过一个最有趣的生日，
because I am the amazing Sporty Man!
因为我就是超级运动侠！
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
Thank you.
谢谢。
Oh-- ohh!
哦——哦！
Oh!
哦！
[grunts]
[咕哝声]
Sporty Man down.
运动侠倒下了。
Anybody else see that coming?
还有人预见到这一幕吗？
- Yeah. - Totally.
- 是的。 - 完全预料到了。
I'm just glad Dad wasn't here to see it.
我只是很庆幸爸爸没在这里看到这一幕。
- Tom, are you okay?
汤姆，你还好吗？
- Oh, my ankle!
哦，我的脚踝！
No matter.
没关系。
Oh, that's my other ankle!
哦，那是我的另一只脚踝！
Stevie, if your party doesn't pick up,
史蒂维，如果你的派对还不热闹起来，
I'm taking my present back.
我就要把我的礼物拿回去了。
Tom, I can handle the party.
汤姆，我能搞定派对。
Okay, everybody, why don't we head into the party room?
好吧，大家，我们为什么不进派对房间呢？
[forced laugh]
[强笑]
Guys, we need to save this party.
伙计们，我们得救救这个派对。
But Mom just said she could handle it.
但是妈妈刚刚说她能搞定。
She laughed and everything.
她还笑了。
[imitating Anne's laugh]
（模仿安妮的笑声）
Is her "I can't handle this" laugh.
那是她的‘我搞不定’的笑声。
Look, this party needs a superhero,
听着，这个派对需要一个超级英雄，
and it's gonna be us.
而那将是我们。
[campy superhero music]
（夸张的超级英雄音乐）
Fear no more, partygoers!
别怕，派对参与者们！
We are here to save the day!
我们来拯救这一天！
I am Kick Chick!
我是踢腿女侠！
I am the Racketeer.
我是球拍侠。
I am the Incredible Bulk.
我是不可思议的巨人。
And I am Goggle Boy.
我是护目镜男孩。
- One! - Two!
- 一！ - 二！
-Three! - Four!
- 三！ - 四！
[all] Is more!
[全体] 还有更多！
- We are... - The Mighty Quad Squad!
- 我们是... - 强大的四人组！
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na, hey! ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐，嘿！ ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
[whistling melody]
♪ [口哨旋律] ♪
♪ ♪
[rhythmic clapping]
[有节奏的拍手]
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Na na na na na-na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
♪ Na na na na na-na, hey! ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐，嘿！ ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na na na na na-na ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ ♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一、二、三、四！ ♪
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
No one can hurt the Incredible Bulk.
没有人能伤害无敌浩克。
Give me everything you've got, Racketeer.
把你所有的本事都拿出来吧，敲诈者。
Feel the wrath of my racket!
感受我球拍的愤怒吧！
Ha. Your pow is powerless.
哈。你的力量是无力的。
[applause]
[掌声]
Though your butt is thick,
尽管你的屁股很厚，
it is no match for Kick Chick.
但它不是踢腿女侠的对手。
I'll make this easy for you.
我会让你轻松点。
It's Kick Chick's duty to kick some booty.
踢腿小鸡的职责就是踢翻一些屁股。
Bam!
砰！
Has she kicked me yet?
她踢到我了吗？
[laughter]
[笑声]
What have you got, Goggle Boy?
你有什么，护目镜小子？
I've got goggles.
我有护目镜。
Goggles are your superpower?
护目镜是你的超能力？
Clear vision is my superpower.
清晰的视野是我的超能力。
[all] Boo!
[所有人] 嘘！
That's it, my present's coming home.
就这样，我的礼物要回家了。
The only good thing about this party is these onions.
这个派对唯一好的地方就是这些洋葱。
Dude, you better step up your superpower.
伙计，你最好提升一下你的超能力。
Seriously, you're stinking up this party
说真的，你把这个派对搞得臭气熏天，
worse than that kid's onion breath.
比那孩子的洋葱口气还糟糕。
Got it.
明白了。
Check out the strap. It's adjustable.
看看这个带子，它是可调节的。
Really?
真的吗？
You gotta up your game, son.
你得提高你的水平，孩子。
Well, you guys took all the good stuff.
好吧，你们把所有好东西都拿走了。
It was either this or Arm Floaties Man.
要么就是这个，要么就是臂浮圈侠。
Okay, who wants cake?
好了，谁想要蛋糕？
Cake, everybody. Come on! [kids cheering]
蛋糕，大家快来！[孩子们欢呼]
It's super-duper superhero cake.
这是超级无敌的超级英雄蛋糕。
Mom got it at the supermarket.
妈妈在超市买的。
Just because you put "super" in front of everything
只是因为你把“超级”放在每样东西前面
doesn't make it a superhero party.
并不代表这就是个超级英雄派对。
Hello!
喂！
- Ugh.
呃。
Nothing super about that breath.
那口气可没什么超级的。
It's like an onion threw up an onion.
简直就像一个洋葱吐出了另一个洋葱。
Those Mighty Quad Squad costumes are too cute. Do you sell them?
那些Mighty Quad Squad的服装太可爱了。你们有卖吗？
I'm sorry, we don't--
对不起，我们没有——
Have them ready yet,
还没有准备好，
but we will starting tomorrow, won't we, Mom?
但从明天开始会有，对吧，妈妈？
Oh, can I preorder one?
哦，我可以预订一件吗？
[gasps] You certainly can.
当然可以。
In fact, we have a special deal, buy two--
实际上，我们有一个特别优惠，买两件——
Get none free.
不送免费。
Hey, kids, who wants to see
嘿，孩子们，谁想看
the amazing Scooter Man pop a wheelie?
神奇的Scooter Man表演翘轮？
Tom, no!
汤姆，不要！
Oh, they're gonna love it, Anne.
哦，他们会喜欢的，安妮。
Whoo!
哇！
[screams]
（尖叫）
[laughter and applause]
（笑声和掌声）
I told you they'd love it, Anne.
我告诉过你会喜欢的，安妮。
[upbeat music]
（欢快的音乐）
Enjoy your costume.
享受你的服装。
Whoa, you guys made your costumes even better?
哇，你们把服装做得更好了？
Yeah, we just beefed them up a little.
是啊，我们稍微加强了一下。
I didn't know we were gonna beef.
我不知道我们要加强。
Yeah, we beefed.
对，我们加强了。
Weren't you there for the beef discussion?
你没参加关于加强的讨论吗？
There was a beef discussion?
有过关于加强的讨论？
Yeah, we talked beef in the car.
是的，我们在车上讨论了加强。
Huh, I guess my earbuds blocked out all the beef banter.
嗯，我猜我的耳机把所有的加强讨论都屏蔽了。
But it's okay, I added to my costume too.
但没关系，我也改进了我的服装。
See? Goggles up, goggles down.
看？护目镜上，护目镜下。
Goggles up, goggles down.
护目镜戴上，护目镜摘下。
You can never guess what Goggle Boy is gonna do next.
你永远猜不到护目镜小子下一步要做什么。
Goggles up?
护目镜戴上？
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, hello.
哦，你好。
And good-bye.
再见了。
Oh, Tom, Tom.
哦，汤姆，汤姆。
Oh, hold on.
哦，等等。
I'll be there in a single bound.
我会一跃而至。
Still bounding.
还在跳跃中。
The kids are geniuses.
孩子们真是天才。
They boxed up $13 worth of supplies
他们把价值13美元的物品打包起来，
and are selling the whole package for 50 bucks.
然后整包以50美元的价格出售。
[laughs]
[笑]
It really is a super value. Enjoy.
这确实是非常划算的。好好享受吧。
[chuckles]
[轻笑]
We've got to get more customers in here and milk this cash cow for all it's got.
我们得吸引更多顾客进来，把这头现金牛榨干。
- Yeah. - Give me the sign.
- 是啊。 - 把牌子给我。
Ha. Hey, kids!
哈。嘿，孩子们！
Oops.
哎呀。
Just--
就这样——
[grunts] This is--
这是——
Okay, listen.
好吧，听着。
Your sales have been heroic,
你们的销售业绩已经很出色了，
but I'm gonna pump them up even more
但我还要让它们更上一层楼
by spinning this sign outside like a pro.
通过像专业人士一样在外面旋转这个牌子。
Check it!
看好了！
Huh? Huh?
嗯？嗯？
Put this down-- Aah! Oh!
把这个放下——啊！哦！
[grunts]
哼！
You know what?
你知道吗？
I think maybe one of you kids should spin it.
我觉得可能你们这些孩子中应该有一个来转这个。
I'm gonna go ice my face.
我要去给我的脸冰敷一下。
And everything else.
还有其他所有地方。
Hmm.
嗯。
If only one of us wasn't busy.
如果有一个我们不忙就好了。
Let's see, busy, busy, busy, Mo.
让我看看，忙，忙，忙，Mo。
Hey, you're it! That's fun.
嘿，轮到你了！真有趣。
Really?
真的吗？
I don't know, it doesn't feel right
我不知道，感觉不太对
splitting up the Mighty Quad Squad.
拆散强大的四人组。
Aw, don't think of it as splitting up the Mighty Quad Squad.
哎，别把它看作是拆散强大的四人组。
Think of it as a heroic gesture
把它看作是一种英雄般的举动
that gives the people what they want.
是为了满足人们的愿望。
Gives the people what they want?
满足人们的愿望？
For example, they want our costumes,
比如说，他们想要我们的服装，
and they don't want yours.
而他们不想要你的。
Fine, I'll be the Mo.
好吧，那我就当莫吧。
Oh, gosh, we've got to restock.
哦，天哪，我们得补货了。
And get more costumes.
还要多弄些服装。
[wind blows]
[风声]
Oh, it's windy.
哦，风好大。
Goggles down.
护目镜戴好。
[scoffs] Goggle Boy looks like
[嗤笑] 护目镜男孩看起来
he's gonna blow away.
好像要被吹走了。
[wind howls]
[风呼啸]
Goggle Boy just blew away!
护目镜男孩被吹走了！
- Anne, we lost one! - What?
- 安妮，我们丢了一个！ - 什么？
[upbeat music]
[轻快的音乐]
Okay, you're okay.
好了，你没事。
You're okay, come on.
你没事的，来吧。
Okay. Okay.
好的，好的。
Nicky, you can let go of the sign now.
尼基，你现在可以放开那个标志了。
No, I can't.
不，我不能。
I hung on so tight when the wind took me,
当风把我吹走时，我抓得太紧了，
now my fingers are stuck.
现在我的手指卡住了。
I'm just glad DiPietro's Wall Oven Pizza
我很高兴DiPietro的墙式烤箱披萨
had that giant inflatable slice for you to land on.
有一个巨大的充气切片让你着陆。
I did a header into a rubber pepperoni.
我一头撞进了一个橡胶意大利辣香肠。
Well, you can relax now, sweetie.
好了，你现在可以放松了，亲爱的。
Come on, kids, help me pry his fingers off the sign.
快点，孩子们，帮我把他手指从招牌上掰开。
Oh, no! Be careful with the pinky.
哦，不！小心他的小指。
It's my favorite.
那是我最喜欢的。
[groans]
（呻吟）
Oh.
哦。
Oh, I'm so embarrassed.
哦，我太尴尬了。
I can't even hold a sign right.
我连个招牌都拿不好。
How am I going to compete with you guys as a superhero?
我怎么能和你们这些超级英雄竞争呢？
[doorbell chimes]
（门铃声）
Forget it, I'm gonna hang up my goggles for good.
算了，我要永远挂起我的护目镜。
There he is.
他来了。
It's Flying Goggle Boy.
是飞行护目镜男孩。
You're the most powerful of the Mighty Quad Squad.
你是强力四人组的头号强者。
Can I have your autograph?
能给我签个名吗？
Really?
真的吗？
Yeah, we saw you fly!
是啊，我们看见你飞了！
What was it like?
那感觉怎么样？
Well, it was quite an adventure.
嗯，那真是一次冒险。
I was walking my usual beat outside the store,
我像往常一样在店外巡逻，
when a cold North wind blew up and filled my cape,
突然一阵北风吹来，吹满了我的斗篷，
sending me high up into the air.
将我高高吹向空中。
I rode that angry wind like a bucking bronco,
我驾驭着那狂怒的风，如同驾驭一匹狂野的野马，
flying higher than any boy has ever flown.
飞得比任何男孩都高。
Once I tamed that blustery beast,
一旦我驯服了那狂风巨兽，
I high-fived the moon,
我和月亮击掌，
fist-bumped the sun,
与太阳碰拳，
then satisfied my superhero-sized appetite
然后用一块15英尺高的披萨，
with a 15-foot-tall slice of pizza.
满足了我的超级英雄般的大胃口。
[all] Whoa.
哇。
Let's hear it for the Mighty Quad Squad!
让我们为强大的四方小队欢呼！
[cheers and applause]
欢呼和掌声
Honey.
亲爱的。
Does that guy look familiar to you?
那个人看起来眼熟吗？
Tom, that's Archibald McAllister,
汤姆，那是阿奇博尔德·麦克斯韦，
the Mayor of Boulderly Hills.
博尔德利山市的市长。
Oh, I've always wanted to hang out with a mayor.
哦，我一直想和市长一起出去玩。
I know.
我知道。
Rub elbows with the fancy people.
和那些上流人士混在一起。
- [chuckles] - Now's my chance.
（轻笑）现在机会来了。
No, Tom. Please don't.
不，汤姆。请不要。
I beg your pardon.
请原谅。
You had some schmutz on your elbow
你的手肘有些脏东西
that could only be removed
只能通过摩擦另一个人的手肘来清除。
by rubbing it with another man's elbow.
哦。
Oh.
我是Tom，来自Tom的运动天地。
I'm Tom, from Tom's Get Sporty.
哦。
- Oh.
市长先生，我能为您做些什么？
What can I do for you, Mr. Mayor?
爸爸！告诉他我想要什么，告诉他！
Tell him what I want, Dad! Tell him, tell him!
好吧，我的儿子Archie想在这个星期六举办一个你的超级英雄生日派对。
All right, my son, Archie, would like one of your superhero birthday parties this Saturday.
太好了。那么，让我们为您报名吧。您不会失望的，阁下。
Great. Well, let's get you signed up.
太好了。那我们开始登记吧。
You won't be disappointed, Your Honor.
您不会失望的，市长先生。
Oh, I don't get disappointed, I get revenge.
哦，我不会失望，我会报复。
You just had to rub elbows with him.
你非得和他套近乎。
Congratulations, Mr. Mayor.
恭喜您，市长先生。
Now with the Mighty Quad Squad
现在有了强大的四重战队
you'll have the strength of four parties.
您将拥有四场派对的力量。
I don't want the Mighty Quad Squad.
我不要强大的四重战队。
I just want Flying Goggle Boy.
我只要飞眼镜侠。
Well, anything for my only child and heir to the throne.
好吧，为了我唯一的儿子，未来的继承人。
Oh, there's-- there's a throne?
哦，有——有一个王座？
Of course not.
当然没有。
The mayor-ship is entirely in the hands of the people.
市长职位完全掌握在人民手中。
- Oh. [laughter]
哦。[笑声]
- You got 'em. - Every time.
你抓住了他们。——每次都是。
All right, so Goggle Boy it is!
好吧，那就决定是护目镜男孩了！
I'm sorry, Mr. Mayor,
对不起，市长先生，
but the Mighty Quad Squad only does our parties together.
但强大的四人组只在我们一起的时候才办派对。
We're a team.
我们是一个团队。
- One. - Two.
一。——二。
Three.
三。
Three!
三！
Three.
三。
Sorry, Squad, the Mo is flying solo.
抱歉，小队，Mo要单飞了。
[all] What?
什么？
Goggle Boy at your service, Mr. Mayor.
Goggle Boy为您服务，市长先生。
Dad, get a picture with me and Goggle Boy.
爸爸，跟我还有Goggle Boy拍张照。
Of course.
当然。
You can't split up the Mighty Quad Squad.
你不能拆散Mighty Quad Squad。
Don't think of it as splitting up.
别想成是拆散。
Think of it as a heroic gesture
把它看作是一种英雄行为
that's giving the people what they want.
这是在满足人们的需求。
Okay, we got it.
好的，我们明白了。
All right, everybody say "Goggle Boy."
好了，大家一起说“Goggle Boy”。
[both] Goggle Boy.
[两人] Goggle Boy。
Ah!
啊！
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
Kick Chick's costume!
Kick Chick的服装！
It's Kick Chick's duty to kick some--
这是Kick Chick的职责，去踢一些——
Oh, come on, everybody loved that yesterday!
哦，拜托，昨天大家都喜欢那个！
Look at him over there, thinking he's so cool
看看他在那儿，以为自己多酷
in those goggles and those yellow boots.
戴着那些护目镜和黄色靴子。
Please, if it wasn't for us letting him use that sign,
请注意，如果不是我们让他使用那个标志，
he never would have flown.
他根本不可能飞起来。
We're the wind beneath his wings.
我们是他的翅膀下的风。
Yeah, and he's not a hero.
是的，他不是英雄。
He's a villain stabbing us in the back.
他是个背后捅我们一刀的恶棍。
I can't believe he ditched us like that.
我简直不敢相信他那样抛弃了我们。
You know, we're his family.
你知道，我们是他的家人。
And he didn't even say he was sorry!
而且他甚至没有说对不起！
Hey, guys, I'm sorry.
嘿，伙计们，对不起。
- No problem. - All good.
- 没问题。- 都好了。
But I'm gonna need more room for my costumes.
但我的戏服需要更多空间。
So if you could move all this junk to the clearance aisle,
所以，如果你们能把这些杂物搬到清仓区，
that would be great.
那就太好了。
You know, it's not fair.
你知道，这不公平。
Your costumes are only selling
你的戏服之所以能卖出去，
because everybody thinks you can fly.
只是因为大家都以为你能飞。
Which you can't.
你不能飞。
Well, it looks like my costumes are flying off the shelves.
嗯，看来我的服装卖得飞快。
Now, if you'll excuse me,
现在，如果你们不介意，
I don't want to keep the Gogglers waiting.
我不想让Gogglers们等太久。
That's what my fans call themselves.
那是我的粉丝们对自己的称呼。
We even have a secret wave.
我们甚至有一个秘密的打招呼方式。
Dee-dee.
Dee-dee。
I'm surprised his goggles
我惊讶他的护目镜
still fit around his big swollen head.
还能套在他那肿大的脑袋上。
No offense.
无意冒犯。
We need to show these kids we're superheroes too.
我们需要向这些孩子们展示我们也是超级英雄。
Yeah, but if we're gonna win them back,
是的，但如果我们想赢回他们，
we have to try something new.
我们必须尝试一些新的东西。
Something different.
一些不同的东西。
Something they've never seen before.
一些他们从未见过的东西。
Here I go.
我来了。
[grunts]
（咕哝声）
Nope.
不行。
But definitely not that.
但绝对不是那样。
Here I go! [grunts]
我来了！（咕哝声）
Nope.
不。
Here I go. [grunts]
我来了。[咕哝声]
Nope.
不。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
See, this heavy-duty fishing line is attached to this sign.
看，这条重型钓鱼线系在这块标牌上。
See?
看到了吗？
And then it runs through this pulley
然后它穿过这个滑轮
that'll be attached to the ceiling.
将会固定在天花板上。
So, when you grab the sign,
所以，当你抓住标牌时，
that's my cue to reel it in and make Goggle Boy fly.
那就是我收线的信号，让护目镜男孩飞起来。
I like it,
我喜欢这个主意，
but is there a way to do it without the fishing line?
但是有没有办法不用钓鱼线就能做到呢？
You know, really make me fly?
你知道，真的让我飞起来？
Um, unfortunately no.
呃，很遗憾，没有。
But the fog will cover the fishing line,
但是雾会掩盖钓鱼线，
so it will look like you're actually flying.
所以看起来你会真的在飞。
Hmm, that's good for now, but in the future
嗯，目前这样不错，但将来
let's look into the real flying thing.
我们还是要研究一下真正的飞行技术。
Ah, it's good to be Goggle Boy.
啊，成为Goggle Boy真好。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
[applause]
[掌声]
Goggles up!
戴上护目镜！
[all] Goggles down!
[所有人] 放下护目镜！
[cheering]
[欢呼声]
If you like that, you'll love Goggle Dog!
如果你喜欢这个，你会爱上护目狗！
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
Can he fly too?
他也能飞吗？
Goggle Dog, ruff, ruff and away!
护目狗，汪汪，飞走吧！
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
Attention, citizens of Archie's birthday party.
注意，阿奇生日派对的市民们。
If you liked Goggle Dog,
如果你喜欢Goggle Dog，
you'll love...
你会爱上...
Utensil Girl!
餐具女孩！
What's going on?
发生什么事了？
Hello, citizens!
大家好！
It is I, Magnet Man!
我就是磁力侠！
What are you two doing?
你们两个在做什么？
I'm fighting crime
我在用吸引力
with the power of attraction!
打击犯罪！
Speaking of attractive,
说到吸引力，
Sticky Fly Strip Boy is here.
粘性苍蝇带男孩在此。
You're interrupting my show.
你打断我的表演了。
Yeah, get out of here, you wannabes.
是啊，走开，你们这些模仿者。
Ugh, I wannabe not smelling that onion breath.
呃，我不想闻到那洋葱味。
It's time for Goggle boy to fly.
是时候让护目镜男孩飞起来了。
Come on, Goggle Boy, fly.
来吧，护目镜男孩，飞吧。
[all] Fly! Fly! Fly!
[所有人] 飞！飞！飞！
Fly! Fly! Fly! Fly!
飞！飞！飞！飞！
I can fly too.
我也能飞。
Uh, me too.
呃，我也是。
Oh!
哦！
Wait, what's happening?
等等，发生了什么？
My magnets are being pulled toward your flatware!
我的磁铁被你的餐具吸过去了！
Guys, let go!
伙计们，放手！
Get out of here!
离开这里！
- We can't. We're magnetized.
我们不能。我们被磁化了。
I want to fly too!
我也想飞！
[all] No, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不。
Great, now your fly strips are stuck to me.
糟糕，现在你的捕蝇条粘在我身上了。
You're ruining my party.
你毁了我的派对。
Just fly already, Goggle Boy.
快飞吧，眼镜小子。
My dad's not paying you
我爸可不是付钱让你
to snuggle up with those super losers.
和那些超级失败者腻在一起的。
Goggle Boy up!
眼镜小子，快上！
Too...much...weight!
太...重...了！
[all groan]
（众人呻吟）
Daddy, he's not flying.
爸爸，他没在飞。
He's embarrassing me in front of all my friends.
他在我所有朋友面前让我难堪。
- Okay, all right.
好吧，好吧。
Hey, I paid you for a flying kid, Harper.
嘿，我付钱给你是要一个会飞的孩子，哈珀。
Make it happen.
让它实现。
Goggle Boy can't fly. He's a sham.
护目镜男孩不会飞。他是个骗子。
[all] Boo!
嘘！
This was my thing, and you couldn't let me have it.
这是我的事，而你不能让我拥有它。
I wasn't just one of the quad for once.
我这次不仅仅是四人组中的一员。
I finally stood out, and you ruined it.
我终于脱颖而出，而你毁了这一切。
[grunts]
（咕哝声）
[both grunting]
（两人同时咕哝）
Wow, he's really upset.
哇，他真的生气了。
Maybe he's right.
也许他说得对。
Some superheroes we are.
我们算什么超级英雄。
We didn't save the day. We destroyed it.
我们没有拯救这一天。我们毁了它。
It's not too late.
还不算太晚。
We have to make this up to him, come on.
我们得补偿他，快点。
[all grunting]
（所有人哼哼声）
Oh, no.
哦，不。
Goggle Boy can't make a fool out of me.
护目镜小子别想让我出丑。
This is my party, and I'll make him cry if I want to.
这是我的派对，如果我想，我会让他哭的。
Onions.
洋葱。
[laughs maniacally]
[狂笑]
It's time to take you where you belong,
是时候把你送到你该去的地方了，
the dumpster.
垃圾桶。
Whoa. [grunts]
哇。[咕哝]
- Nicky! - Stop!
- 尼基！ - 停下！
We're sorry.
对不起。
[grunting] - Come on.
[咕哝] - 来吧。
[all groan]
[所有人呻吟]
We didn't mean to ruin things for you.
我们不是故意要破坏你的事情。
We were just jealous, and we went too far.
我们只是嫉妒，做得太过分了。
What do you say?
你说呢？
Goggle Boy goes back in there
Goggle Boy 再进去
and gives the people what they want?
给人们他们想要的？
Forget it.
算了吧。
I don't deserve the spotlight. I was kidding myself.
我不配站在聚光灯下。我一直在自欺欺人。
I can't really fly anyway.
反正我也不能真的飞。
Okay. It's okay, kids.
好了。没关系，孩子们。
It's all just part of the show.
这一切都只是表演的一部分。
[forced laughter]
[勉强的笑声]
Ugh.
呃。
Smells like trouble in the new party room.
新派对房间里弥漫着麻烦的气息。
Come on!
快点！
Aah!
啊！
Anne, is that you?
安妮，是你吗？
No, it's the Mayor.
不，是市长。
Oh.
哦。
Anne has shoes just like these.
安妮也有一双这样的鞋子。
Ow, it stings.
哎呀，好疼。
I can't see anything.
我什么也看不见。
I never thought I'd say this,
我从未想过我会这么说，
but we need someone with goggles.
但是我们需要一个戴护目镜的人。
- Goggle Boy, save us!
护目侠，救救我们！
But I'm not really a superhero.
但我并不是真正的超级英雄。
Today...
今天...
You are.
你是。
Remain calm!
保持冷静！
I can see clearly that you all need help.
我清楚地看到你们都需要帮助。
Hurry, Goggle Boy!
快点，护目侠！
You're the only one that can save us!
你是唯一能救我们的人！
Or am I?
还是我？
One, two,
一，二，
three, four.
三，四。
[all] Is more!
[所有人] 还有更多！
Goggles down.
护目镜放下。
Follow me into the fog, Mighty Quad Squad.
跟我进入迷雾，强大的四人组。
Okay, kids, one hand on your eyes,
好了，孩子们，一只手放在眼睛上，
the other on the shoulder in front of you.
另一只手放在前面人的肩膀上。
Grab onto my cape, and I'll lead you out.
抓住我的斗篷，我会带你们出去。
It's safe now. You can breathe normally.
现在安全了。你们可以正常呼吸了。
- Thank you, Goggle boy. You saved us.
谢谢你，护目镜男孩。你救了我们。
You really are a superhero!
你真的是个超级英雄！
Well, it wasn't just me.
嗯，不只是我一个人。
It was the Mighty Quad Squad.
这是我们强大的四方小队的功劳。
[cheers and applause]
（欢呼和掌声）
Well, I will spread the word at city hall
我会在市政厅宣传你们的伟大事迹。
about your great parties.
关于你们举办的精彩派对。
Thank you, Mr. Mayor.
谢谢你，市长先生。
And as for you...
至于你...
[laughter]
（笑声）
You've escaped the onion fog this time,
这次你逃过了洋葱雾，
but you haven't seen the last of me,
但你们还没见过我的最后一面，
Mighty Quad Squad.
强大的四人组。
- Oh. - Eww.
- 哦。 - 哎呀。
Okay, Junior, let's go home and get you a mint.
好吧，小家伙，我们回家给你拿片薄荷糖。
- Thank you.
- 谢谢你。
- Oh, no. - Hmm?
- 哦，不。 - 嗯？
It looks like the onion fog is creeping in from the next room.
看起来洋葱雾正从隔壁房间悄悄蔓延过来。
I forgot to turn off the fog machine.
我忘了关掉雾机。
Well, you're never gonna find it now.
好吧，你现在永远找不到它了。
This looks like a job for the Mighty Quad Squad!
这看起来是强大四人组的工作！
[all] Four is more!
四人同心，其力断金！
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
[whistling melody]
[口哨旋律]
♪ ♪
[vocalizing]
[发声]
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ 耶 ♪
[vocalizing]
[发声]
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ 耶 ♪